moondogsports.com 2011-01-28

# Privacy Policy | MoonDog Sports

MoonDogSports.com takes the privacy of our subscribers and users very seriously. This policy describes how we handle the information you provide us when you visit or subscribe to the site.

During the course of operating this web site, MoonDogSports.com does drop cookies, small text files, onto your hard drive. This is to allow us to recognize you as a subscriber or user and allows us to compile statistical data pertaining to the site’s usage. 

Any personal information gathered will remain with MoonDogSports.com and will not be sold, leased, lent, shared, or leaked to any third parties for marketing purposes without your express permission.

However, we may disclose information you provide if required to do so by law or if we have a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process served on us; (2) protect and defend our rights or property; or (3) act in an emergency to protect someone’s safety.

We have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. These include a firewall to prevent unauthorized access to our systems and maintenance of registration information in a separate database. Although we will exercise reasonable care in providing secure transmission of information between your computer and our servers, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us over the Internet and we accept no liability for any unintentional disclosure.

We maintain archives of our web logs, database, and other systems and information. Please note that it is possible some of this information may remain archived after we delete the information from its active database (see above regarding web logs). We maintain archives for disaster recovery, legal and other non-marketing purposes.

If you are visiting our site from outside the United States, please be advised that because we operate internationally, and certain of our computer systems are currently based in the United States, your personal data will be processed by us in the U.S. where data protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in other parts of the world, such as the European Union. By using the Web Site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

We do not retrieve any information from a computer unrelated to our site or services. Our third party advertisers may place a cookie as part of serving ads on our site.

All communication on the Internet takes place between pairs of IP Addresses. Our Web servers will log the IP address from which any connection is made. We may use these IP addresses to help diagnose technical problems or prevent abuse of our systems or other site users.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [**here**](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

—————————————————————————————–

**Google**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
Google’s use of the [**DART**](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network [**privacy policy**](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

—————————————————————————————-

**Adify Corporation** : Privacy Policy  
Version 1.2 – August 2007

Adify Corporation (Adify) provides an online advertising sale and display service (the “Service”) for Internet “Publishers”. We enable “Advertisers” to place advertisements via the Service on one or more sites belonging to Publishers. We enable “Network Operators” to create and manage networks of Publishers and Advertisers using tools we provide. The Service runs on software developed and hosted by Adify, its subsidiaries, and third-party contractors.

Adify Corporation recognizes the importance of information privacy. This Privacy Policy describes Adify’s practices for gathering, storing, using and disseminating information, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard that information. We may change this policy from time to time. All changes will be posted to this site, and you are encouraged to periodically check back to this site for any changes to the privacy policy.

A. INFORMATION COLLECTION

You can browse certain areas of the Service without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. For example, your user ID is displayed throughout the Service and is therefore available to the public. If you choose to provide us with personal information, you consent to the transfer and storage of that information to our servers located in the United States.

If you are an Advertiser, Publisher, or Network Operator, Adify requests certain information related to your business, your website, and your use of the Service. Adify will collect and store this information. Adify may collect your email addresses, mailing and billing address and order information, IP address, information about your site, including but not limited to your site’s page impressions, advertising prices and information about your visitors.

To improve and personalize the Service, Adify may collect information about your business from third parties and provide this information on your behalf. This information may include, but is not limited to the following: third-party counts of monthly page views, visitor composition, and rankings in various indices. Adify may not provide you the option to turn off the presentation of this information.

Adify may collect tax information, including Value Added Tax (VAT) or federal tax ID numbers. Adify will collect information regarding your activities with respect to the Service. Adify will collect any comments you send to us and any information you post to the Adify site or on a Publisher site. Adify may also collect information through the use of Cookies (see below). Adify collects personal information when you: (1) register with Adify to become a Publisher or Advertiser, (2) provide comments or submit a problem to Adify, (3) request information from Adify and provide your name or return contact information, or (4) respond to special offers, contests or surveys. As part of the registration process, you may be asked to provide contact information and other personally identifying information.

B. COOKIES

“Cookies” are small data files that may be downloaded to your computer when you visit the Adify site or a Publisher site and permit the Adify server to identify your browser whenever you interact with the Adify site or with an Adify Publisher site. Adify uses cookies to recognize repeat visits by users of its Service and to collect information about its users’ interactions with the Services. These cookies contain identification information that enables us to streamline a user’s experiences using the Services and to report such information to Publishers, Advertisers, and Network Operators. You may set your browser software to reject cookies, but you may not be able to optimize the features of the Services. In some cases, you may not be able to access Services if cookies are disabled.

C. USE AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience.

1) If you are a Publisher we may share information about your site, including but not limited to page impressions, site traffic, prices and readership with Advertisers, Publishers, Network Operators. We will not share personally identifiable information about you with Advertisers without your prior written or electronic consent.

2) If you are an Advertiser we may disclose your contact information and email address to Publishers on whose Sites you have placed advertisements.

3) If you are a Publisher we may disclose your contact information and email address to Network Operators managing Networks that sell advertising on your behalf.

4) If you are a User we may share aggregated, non-personally identifiable information about you with Publishers or Advertisers, such as the number of users who visit a Publisher site or the number of users who clicked on a particular advertisement. This information does not identify you individually. Further, we encourage you to review the privacy policies of the Publishers that you visit. You should contact Publishers directly and review their privacy policies should you have questions concerning their use of your information such as, for example, communications you may or may not wish to receive.

5) Disclosure for Marketing Purposes. We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent.

6) Other Disclosures. Adify may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or if Adify has a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary to protect and/or defend the rights and interests of Adify. Adify may, as permitted by applicable law, disclose your personally identifiable information to Publishers, Advertisers, Network Operators, or third parties in connection with an investigation of fraud, infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity and you expressly authorize Adify to make such disclosures.

7) Domestic and International Use. All personally identifying information collected by Adify may be used in the United States or, if the Service are undertaken by Adify for a non-US Publisher, Advertiser, or Network Operator, such information may be transferred to that Publisher, Advertiser, or Network Operator,outside of the United States, and through your use of the Service you hereby consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

8)Merger or Acquisition. If Adify Corporation is merged or acquired by another entity, personally identifiable information may be transferred to such entity as a part of the merger or acquisition.

D. REVIEW AND MODIFICATIONS TO YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION.

If you are a Publisher, Advertiser, or Network Operator, you may add, modify or update your email address, payment information, name, mailing address, preferences for the types of notifications you wish to receive from Adify, and other information by accessing the “Account” page on the Service. Other personal information may be modified or updated by accessing by contacting Adify as set forth in Section H below. Adify may retain transactional history in order to document a transaction you may have had with an Adify Publisher, Advertiser, or Network Operator. You should contact the Publisher, Advertiser, or Network Operator directly in order to access, modify or update your personal information with them, if any.

We do retain personal information from suspended and closed accounts in order to comply with law, prevent fraud, collect any unpaid fees, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Terms & Conditions, and take other actions otherwise permitted by law.

E. LINKS TO OTHER SITES

As a part of the Service, Adify provides links to sites operated by third parties. Adify is not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices or the content of those third party sites.

F. INFORMATION SECURITY

Adify stores personally identifiable information obtained through registration securely and considers it part of the assets of its business. All information is stored in our secure servers located inside the United States. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain accuracy of information, and ensure the appropriate use of information, Adify has put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information it collects online. However, information security is a constantly evolving art and science, and no information is completely secure.

Your password is the key to your Adify account. Use unique numbers, letters, and special characters, and do not disclose your Adify password to anyone, even an Adify representative. If you do share your password or your personal information with others, remember that you are responsible for all actions taken in the name of your account. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately notify Adify and change your password.

G. CHILDREN

Adify uses reasonable efforts not to collect, use or disclose individually identifiable information from children under the age of 13. The Service is not targeted at children, and children may not use the Service.

H. FURTHER INFORMATION

If you have any questions about anything in this Privacy Policy, or about collection of personally identifiable information, or information generally, please contact Adify via help@adify.com or:

Corporate Headquarters  
1000 Cherry Avenue, Suite 200  
San Bruno, CA 94066  
USA

Your use of MoonDogSports.com, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this Privacy Policy. By using MoonDogSports.com, you are accepting the practices set out in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the changes on this page. Please check the revision date at the bottom of this page to determine if the statement has been modified since you last reviewed it. Your continued use of any portion of MoonDogSports.com following posting of the updated Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes. 

If you have any questions, use the Contact MoonDog link found on this site’s navigation bar. 

Privacy Policy: 22 March 2009
